http://www.thegrand.com/privacy/

Buy Tickets   | 800.821.1894 | 409.765.1894   |  2020 Postoffice St,  Galveston TX 77550
Home »
Privacy Policy – The Grand 1894 Opera House
»
Privacy Policy
Want create site? With Free visual composer you can do it easy.PRIVACY POLICY
We have created this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.
Why did you receive a mailing from us?
Our email marketing is permission based. If you received a mailing from us, our records indicate that (a) you have expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future (“opt-in”), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings. If you believe you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to tickets@thegrand.com for review.
How can you stop receiving emails or other information from us?
Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply click the Unsubscribe or Update Profile links included in the email. You may also contact us by phone 800-821-1894 or 409-765-1894, and by mail The Grand, 2020 Postoffice Street, Galveston, TX 77550
The Information We Collect:
This privacy notice applies to all information collected or submitted on The Grand’s website or through our Box Office. The types of personal information collected are: Name, Address, email address, phone number, Credit/Debit Card information, etc.
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift certificate or make an IMO/IHO donation which requires the recipient’s contact information, you may need to submit the recipient’s Name, Address, Phone Number, etc.
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only for use related to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order or to notify the person(s) in the event of performances changes or cancellation.
How we protect your privacy
We use appropriate security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system.
Sharing and Usage
We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone for their promotional use without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information, and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.
Did you find apk for android? You can find new Free Android Games and apps.
Stay in Touch!
In The News
Five Historic Texas Theaters Share Their Strategies for Survival
Texas Highways
Search for:
2019-2020 Performing Arts Season Overview for Patron’s Choice
Happy Trails – Special Offer!
The Choir of Man Debuts in US!
Subscribe to our email newsletter today to receive updates on the latest shows,news and special offers!
Thanks for signing up. You must confirm your email address before we can send you. Please check your email and follow the instructions.
We respect your privacy. Your information is safe and will never be shared.
×
This is a special one time offer!
×
